Hello! I'm Konoka Matsuda!
Konoka Matsuda style home training!
For those who want to lose weight for the coming summer season.
or for those who just want to build up their fitness.
I, Matsuda, have come up with a menu myself.
I hope we can all work together to build a beautiful body!
So let's get started!
Let's go!
Let's work on your stomach and core!
First of all, we're going to lift our legs vertically off the floor, keeping our hips off the floor.
If you can, try lowering them to just above the floor.
Breathe well.
Lift your head lightly and look at your feet to prevent your hips from bending too far back.
Now, 15 seconds, exhale, inhale, exhale, exhale.
Go for it.
All right. - All right.
Now we're going to do a plank core exercise, and we're going to work together for one minute.
Palms on the floor.
Keep a straight line from your head to your heels.
As you get tighter, your hips tend to bend naturally.
Try to keep a firm grip on your abdomen.
Planks are quite simple and I'm not very good at them myself.
Let's persevere and work hard together.
I don't regret it, but let's endure and do our best together.
How about the other half? It's getting hotter and hotter.
I'm not regretting it, but we'll do our best to endure it together.
I'm just trying to endure. It's tough, but just hang on for another 15 seconds or so.
I can do it!
Just a little more.
Good! Good job!
Wow, you're getting tired.
Now, for the last event of the first song, here's a twisting plank.
We're going to go from the plank shape you did before, to swaying your hips from side to side and touching the floor.
Lift your hips up as far as you can, as if you were drawing a mountain with your hips.
No, this is really hard.
It's really hard to do the same plank in the same position.
This one's really tough, too.
Good luck, everyone.
For about 20 seconds.
Go!
This is the last of the first song.
Let's push it just a little bit further.
Ten more seconds! Come on!
One, two, one, two.
Is this the end of the first song?
I'm sure this is exhausting, but if you're still going for it, let's push even harder from here.
Okay, I'll do my best too.
Let's start with right-angle sit-ups, where you do sit-ups while keeping your legs at right angles.
Lift your body up as if you're holding your whole neck in the palm of your hand.
I'm one of those people whose knees tend to come closer and closer to the body.
Try to make a right angle.
Go for it.
Five seconds to go.
Okay, okay.
Good luck, guys.
Next up, torsion sit-ups.
Try to cross-touch your left and right elbows and knees alternately.
If you can already touch them, just touch them.
Shake your head left and right as you do it.
If you can lift your upper body as much as possible, you'll get more out of it.
Go for it! Five more seconds!
Go!
Here we go.
Next one's pretty tough, but let's go for it.
Next, we're going to do the leg lifts.
Put your hands under your body and thrust your feet into the ceiling.
Then slide your legs straight up so that they don't touch the floor.
Again, if you look at your feet when you're extending your legs, it's harder for your hips to turn.
No, this is probably the hardest.
Come on, guys, you're almost there.
Come on.
Breathe out.
Okay, we're almost there.
Just a little bit more, just a little bit more. Let's push the envelope.
Here we go.
Now it's time for the thump-thump touch.
Twist your body and touch the floor on both sides.
If it's too tight, you can put your feet on the floor.
Go for it, everyone, get to the waist, go for it.
You're doing great, you're doing great.
Almost there.
One, two, one, two, one, two.
All right, now, last one.
Let's do a run-through.
Let's do this until the end of this song.
Now, this is really the last event.
Running-in.
Imagine your knees touching your belly button while you're running.
Let's do it with your stomach.
I'll do it till the end of the song.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Come on.
Almost there.
Just a little more.
Hang in there.
Good, good, good.
Five.
Forty-three.
Two.
One.
Are we done?
I'm so tired.
How was it?
You've all worked very hard.
We'll continue with this.
From now on, I'd like to work with you all
I hope we can make beautiful buddies together.
I'm so tired!
I'm going to work hard at home, too, watching this.
Let's all work hard together.
Thank you all for your hard work, you've all worked really hard.
If you keep doing this every day, I think you'll be able to achieve your goal of becoming a Nobody.
And gradually...
It's not so hard.
It's not so hard anymore.
I'm tired and my speech is not smooth anymore.
I think it'll stop being hard.
Let's work together.
Subscribe to my channel and click the Good button.
Thank you very much.